WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
Hey, Pervy Sage. What Jutsu are you
gonna teach me this time?
The last time was Walk-on-Water Jutsu,
so is it gonna be Walk-on-Fire Jutsu?
Or maybe Walk-in-the-Air?
Hurry up and tell me, Pervy Sage!
You keep calling me Pervy Sage.
So you have no idea that
I'm a superb person, huh?
Huh...? A superb Pervy Sage?
Listen carefully!
Toad Sage is only a disguise!
As a matter of fact...!
North and South and East and West!
I'm the white-maned toad charmer,
and one of the legendary Sannin whom
even celestial beings can't defeat.
Such a stud!
That he strikes fear...
in the hearts of people!
I am no other than "Jiraiya-sama"!
Yes...
I'm talking about me!
Huh...
Oh, No-!
Jiraiya's Woman Trouble,
Naruto's Trouble
Atafuku Town?
That's ten kilometers from here!
It's "O"tafuku Town!
Hey... hey...
Hey, Pervy Sage!
I'm telling you, it's Jiraiya.
Gimme a break...
So the fact that such
a bigwig Pervy Sage like you
is taking me along as
his travel companion means...
that I'm potentially a genius?
Just as I thought!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Why did you choose me?
A long time ago,
the Fourth Hokage was my disciple.
And you resemble the Fourth Hokage
so much, it's almost funny.
That's the only reason...
I...?
The Fourth Hokage...?
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
W-What is it?
Yeah!
The fact that I resemble
the Fourth Hokage means
that I also possess genius
of his level, right?
I'll become the Hokage, after all!
All right!
W-Wait...
I stepped on some dog poop!
About the only areas you resemble
the Fourth Hokage
are your hair and your stubbornness!
What was that?!
You senile Pervy Sage!
Not again!
Sakura? Come here!
Okay!
Please take these rice sweets
over to Ino-chan's house.
Ino's house?
These?
That's right...
Don't bother them
by staying too long.
Because everyone is
very busy at this time.
I know that!
See you later!
Oh, yeah...
I'll bring some over
to Sasuke-kun later on too.
I wonder if he likes sweets...?
And to Naruto too...
Naruto looks like
he would eat anything...
Hey Kakashi-sensei!
Teach me Chidori too!
You may say teach me,
but it's not that easy.
What the hell's that?!
That's not fair, show me how!
Teach it to me.
Sasuke-kun... Thank you...
You rescued me from
the Sand Ninja, right?
No...
Huh?
For a start, why don't you try gathering
Chakra in your palms!
All right!
The person who rescued you...
was Naruto.
Like this? Like this?
Oh come on, Sasuke-kun,
you're being overmodest again.
It's true that Naruto has gotten stronger,
but against that Sand Ninja...
I'm telling you the truth.
That kid fought desperately
to rescue you.
He showed a kind of strength that
he had never shown before.
Naruto rescued... me.
Oh, it's coming...
Chidori! Huh? Chidori! Chidori!
All right! I'll bring some to Naruto too!
I wasn't...
I wasn't able to do anything...
I don't want to watch a precious comrade
die right before my eyes ever again...
No matter what,
I will protect you!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto is getting stronger and stronger.
Compared to him, I...
While you may able to
manage against him,
I couldn't possibly...
He's on a completely different level...
Yeah...
If we go at each other,
we'll either both be killed or at best,
kill each other simultaneously.
Even if we increased the numbers,
that wouldn't change.
I didn't expect the kid's guard
would be a legendary Sannin.
With him as the opponent...
the names of Leaf Village's Uchiha Clan
and the Seven Ninja Swordsmen
of Mist would be tarnished.
Yeah. However...
Any strong one has a weakness...
Stop! You will get cursed!
Hey, hey, Pervy Sage...
Huh?!
What kind of a student was
the Fourth Hokage?
Well, I guess one could say
that he developed to that extent
because he was my student...
You're one lucky guy
to be taught by me!
— Hmmm...
Are you dubious?
A good teacher will develop
good disciples.
That goes without saying.
Then, then, who taught you,
Pervy Sage?
Me?
I learned from the Third Hokage.
The Third Hokage?
That's right...
The Third Hokage was
still young and lively.
— The Third Hokage... young and lively?
That's right!
I was young and lively too!
Young and lively?!
I... I got tangled up.
See... You got cursed...
So you learned from Kakashi.
Then you experienced
the "Bell Training," right?
Huh...?
Yeah! I did! Yes I did!
Only I was tied to the tree trunk
and had one deuce of a time...
What? You too?
Huh? What do you mean
by "you too"?
Huh?
What do you mean by "you too"?
Why don't you just hurry,
get up and return those things.
Even if you were to say that...
it's pretty difficult...
There are two bells.
The fact that there are
only two means...
That one of us has to go
to the tree trunk...
You're quick on the uptake, Orochimaru.
All right! I'll make it!
Come at me with the intent to kill!
Jiraiya, I won the bet with you, didn't I?
You got tied to the tree trunk,
after all.
Shut up!
You flat-chested like a cutting board.
What did you say?!
You nerdy perv!
Okay, Okay, that's enough.
Tsunade and Orochimaru go home!
Okay!
You are hopeless...
Ninja shouldn't be getting caught in
obvious traps like that over and over again.
But...
Why don't you learn a little
from Orochimaru?!
Sarutobi-sensei, you're always
saying Orochimaru, Orochimaru!
Hm?
When it comes to snooping,
I'm really good at Transparency Jutsu.
Gimme a break...
I don't even wanna know
what level of Transparency Jutsu
you possess...
I've never been caught once!
And that's the truth!
If you're that sure of yourself,
I'll go with you next time...
You're such a lecher, Sarutobi-sensei...
Huh?! Huh?
What, what?
Hey!
What's so funny?! Pervy Sage!
Huh?
It's just as I said, a good teacher
will develop good disciples.
Huh...? I don't understand
what you're saying!
Come on, let's go.
Did you put it back properly?
Yeah, I fixed them!
See!
It appears that they haven't
found Naruto yet.
But don't you think that's strange?
Those guys had already
infiltrated the village.
It should be easy to find Naruto
in this village.
Itachi knows Naruto's face.
Kakashi...
Why is Kakashi sleeping?
Besides, only Jonin are gathering here...
What are you doing?
What in the world happened?!
Nothing... in particular...
Is it true that that
Itachi has returned?!
And moreover,
that he's after Naruto...?!
Oh...
Idiot...
Why does this always happen?!
So that guy returned to this village?
And moreover, he's pursuing Naruto?
What does all this mean?!
Sasuke-kun?!
Where's Naruto?!
Huh? I just got here too.
I wanted to give Naruto...
Some sweets...?
If Naruto is caught by that guy,
that will spell his end.
I'm not gonna let him do that!
Hey, old man!
Naruto must have come here!
And do you know
where he went after that?
Oh, Naruto, right...
If I remember correctly...
Jiraiya-san came here
around noon and...
They ate ramen together,
and he said he was going somewhere...
Where?!
Hmm... I think he said to a post station
some distance from the village...
And then he left with Jiraiya-san.
Jiraiya?
Jiraiya — one of the genius Sannin.
Well, in appearance,
he just looks like
a big white-haired old man.
Big and white-haired...
H-Hey!
Jeez... If you're gonna
ask somebody a question,
it's only polite to stay
and have a ramen or something.
Candies are here.
This town is pretty weird.
Naruto!
Huh?
We're staying here tonight!
What?! I can still walk!
A disciple should obey his master!
I just want to learn the Jutsu!
That's what's called a disciple!
Huh?!
Oh, oh...!
Naruto!
Yes?
Here, this is the key to the room.
Go to the room ahead of me,
practice Chakra,
train some and go to sleep!
— Got it?!
— What?!
"The adult world is gonna begin
from this point on"...
Is that the vibe, Pervy Sage?!
That's not fair!
That post town isn't that far...!
This! Somehow this always happens
when I'm with that Pervy Sage!
Damn...
Here...
"Missed"
Candies are here!
I've got to check door by door!
Cheers!
I wonder if he really has any inclination
to oversee my training?
What about that one? Yeah that.
See! A hundred out of a hundred!
Do you have a blond kid with
a dumb-looking face, about my age
and a big white-haired old man
staying here?
This is an inn for women only...
I'm looking for someone...
Do you have a blond kid with
a dumb-looking face, about my age
and a big white-haired old man
staying here?
Today, we only have old people.
Hmm... this is kind of crisp
on the tongue...
Hey, why are you guys all sleeping?
Do you have a blond kid with
a dumb-looking face, about my age
and a big white-haired old man
staying here?
White-haired...?
Are they here?!
Eh... Do I remember seeing
some people like that earlier
when shifts changed...?
This tastes bitter...
are you all right with it? Cheers!
Oh! A blond kid and
a white-haired old man!
They're here?!
What's their room number!
Um...
Room number one at
the end of the hallway
on the second floor...
What's up?
Has she already dumped you?
Okay, okay!
Okay, okay, I'll open up!
Naruto!
It's not him...
gaman no renzoku dattaro
a cycle of hardship, right?
kokoro de naiteita ndarou
inside, we were crying, right?
jibun de kimeta sono yume dake wa yuzurenai ndarou
but the one thing we won't give up is the dream we've chosen, right?
wakiyaku dakedo
it's a secondary role
kage no hito dakedo
a role in the shadows
yume to mukiau toki kurai
but in reaching for that dream
man naka ni isasete shoujiki ni isasete
let us stay centered, let us stay true
ima made nandomo nan toka akiramezu ni
over and over, we hung on without giving up
ima made nandomo tachi agatte kita janai ka
over and over, we kept coming back up
ima made nandomo
over and over, we believed and dreamed
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mite nandomo
ima made nandomo baka o mite kita janai ka
over and over, we've seen fools
ima made nandomo hito no kage ni tatte kita janai ka
over and over, we've stood in the shadows of others
saa shuyaku da yo jibun no yume kurai wagamama de isasete
now, it's our turn... let us bask in our dreams
Damn it! My body is frozen!
What is this creepy feeling?
This guy is absolutely not
an ordinary person.
He's got the same Sharingan
as Sasuke.
He's a member of Uchiha clan.
Is this the guy Sasuke
was talking about?
Next time:
"Growl Chidori, Roar Sasuke!"